Parry!
Oh, come on.
I don't think I'm exactly hero material.
Instructor Noor!
Instructor!
Uh
She Vert Guerrfire I don't
think of this there, are you!
How do you find, what do you
feel? Were you a pawn for?
Take your push!
I'll be back to the end of the day.
If it's not a dream, it's not a dream.
I'll never get to the end of the day.
Thank
you
so
much for watching.
I don't believe it. Are you hurt?
I'm all right. I'm fine.
Ah, it all makes so much sense to me now.
Thank you, Rolo, for all your help. What?
What are you talking about?
The dragon calmed down
just like you told it to.
You really saved my butt. What?
No, I didn't. It wasn't me.
What?
Come on.
It totally just stopped
attacking all of a sudden.
Oh, you know it was because of you.
No way!
That definitely wasn't me!
Oh.
There are people out there scared of my
power and really hate that I have it.
Oh, okay.
The dragon is docile now,
but it knew Rolo could control it
no matter how ferocious it got.
It was intimidated.
I getcha.
Whatever you say, Rolo.
We'll just leave it at that.
Okay.
Well, since that's done, can I
maybe ask you for a favor? I guess.
I know this might sound a little odd,
but could you send this dragon
back to where it came from?
We cannot let it go.
It's too dangerous.
For sure.
Logic tells us that we should probably
just kill the thing right now.
I mean, even I know that.
But if we could, I really
don't want to kill this fella.
I know it's kind of
selfish of me to say that
but could you maybe
just cut it some slack?
Okay ah if that's what you really want
Rolo, can you do it?
I'm not sure.
I mean, given how powerful it is!
The best I can do is just ask nicely.
It's alright.
You're safe, Kay.
Neither of them are afraid of you.
Okay, here I go.
Oh, uh.
What is it, Rolo?
It said it would do anything.
its master orders.
Uh, master?
This dragon really said that to you?
Wow, this hardly seems real.
I don't believe it.
Crazy to think such a massive
creature would call Rolo its master.
Well, then... Go for it.
Tell the big guy to pack up and quietly
go back to wherever it came from.
Oh, also, while we're at it, tell it not
to mess with any more humans, please.
Yeah, okay.
I can try.
It understands.
It's going to agree to
everything you asked for.
Wow, that's amazing!
Yeah, it sure is.
It's gone.
Yeah.
Oh!
Whoa!
Well, it couldn't have worked out
any more in our favor than that.
Even a dragon that has
lived for thousands of
years Riz is still a
stupid beast in the end.
Nothing more than my pawn.
I thought nothing would
be left of the capital.
Well, fine.
Commence attack. Yes, sir.
Hmm.
You are certain this will bring
an end to the Clay's kingdom?
Because I am not backing down.
A well-known beast tamer
has already awakened
the Dragon of Calamity
and brought it to heal.
I guess it was worth the
exorbitant price they demanded.
And of course, after the dragon goes
on a rampage, our forces will follow.
All foot soldiers will be equipped
with magic swords and magic shields,
while the elite troops will have
magic armor and magic cannons.
Furthermore,
we'll have three Aegises,
the mobile mana bulwark generation device,
and four of the ultra-high output mana
ray weapons, the devastating Brionacal.
Just splendid.
Excellent work.
Please wait, Your Majesty.
Out with it?
What have you to say, Rondaeus?
Pardon my bluntness,
but I just do not see how this war can
possibly benefit our country in the long run.
That is enough.
I beg you to reconsider.
Know your place.
I said I've heard enough.
No one can threaten us.
We stand at the forefront of
technology and magical prominence.
And we will make sure
the whole world knows it.
In the near future, people will tell
but one tale of the Klai's kingdom.
It was a country of fools who neglected
proper upkeep of the Dungeon of the Lost,
led down a path to ruin by
their own selfish greed.
Meanwhile,
we shall be remembered as
the humanitarian force that
liberated the people from
their imbecile of a monarch.
History has no need for
multiple storytellers.
One truth is all the people can handle.
This way.
See? It's over there.
Okay.
Is it alive?
I don't know.
We need to get closer.
Instructor!
It's the Magical Empire.
Prepare to fire. Yes, sir.
Your Majesty, take a look.
Yes, what is it?
That is the princess, is it not?
Next to her is Ines, the Divine Shield.
One of the living legends
known all around the world.
Perhaps she is the reason
why the royal capital
has not been completely
razed to the ground.
Isn't this perfect?
Because the era where legends
rule has come to an end.
We now live in an era that is
defined by those with wisdom.
Fire the Brionac at them immediately!
Yes, sir.
She may be the divine shield,
but the heat of the Brionac
will evaporate her into nothing.
Yet another one of their so-called
legends will die horrifically by my hand.
Ah, what beautiful bliss.
This is why I simply adore war.
Ready!
The Brionac is prepared to launch!
Everything is prepared, sir!
Fire!
This is the end.
What's that?
Lady Lindbergh, please, stand back. Rolo!
Mary!
Wait, what just happened?
There must have been a misfire due to a
problem with the mana condensation process.
You half-wits!
Prepare the next one immediately!
Oh, that was too close.
What the heck was that light?
And oh my gosh, look at all those people.
You said that was the Imperial Army?
Looks like Dorytus III
has mobilized his troops.
It's like he has an
endless supply of warriors.
I don't understand what's happening here.
All I can say is Dorytus
has brought this force
with the purpose of
destroying our kingdom.
What?
We have our army at the Capitol,
but not enough for those numbers.
Lady Lindbergh, we should go now.
We are of no use here.
I agree.
Let's go back and meet up with my brother.
What do you think, Instructor?
Given the situation, do you need to ask?
There's really no choice but
to get our butts out of here.
Yes, I understand.
That was silly of me.
Why is she smiling?
You'd think she'd be more terrified.
I...
obviously we should...
Attack's incoming!
Everyone behind me!
Divine shield!
Well, this is aggravating.
Your Majesty, please.
You might want to take cover in the rear.
Finish the job quickly!
They're gonna keep us
pinned here like this.
Guess there's only really one way out.
Instructor, what is it?
I'm going to buy us some time.
I'll get all their
attention focused on me.
You can use that as a chance to escape.
That's what you want to do?
I'm not great at fighting,
but running away?
There, I'm kind of an expert.
I used to go hunting for honeycomb all the
time and was always
getting attacked by bees.
If I just run around like
crazy, things will work out.
I'm going to be fine.
I plan on coming back
alive, so don't worry.
Um, okay,
but at least allow me to offer you the
one thing I can do to help, all right?
Sure, go right ahead.
Must be some defense magic. Here we go.
Prepare for impact.
What? Impact? What do you mean?
I promised to control the output
this time, so don't worry.
It'll be okay.
Hold on a sec, Lin.
I didn't mean going on some kind of
crazy suicide mission. Over there!
There's another one of those lights!
The next one's on its way!
We're leaving everything in your
hands, Instructor! Go forth!
And Godspeed! Oh, crap!
I'm not ready for the impact!
Physical enhancement!
Wind blast!
Oh,
man!
Thank God I'm alive!
Perry!
Good to know I can deflect those.
In that case, Perry!
It's working!
My momentum is too strong to change
course, so here goes nothing.
I'll take it as far as I can.
Perry!
The more time I can buy, the
better chance they have to escape.
I'm just going to run around and
parry every single thing I see.
Parry!
What the hell?
Our weapons are gone!
Hey, what happened?
Where'd my weapon go?
They're up there!
Defend yourselves!
I don't have a shield!
What are those up in the air?
What the devil just happened?
What is this?
What's going on?
What the hell is happening?
Hey wait a second were you not this just
doesn't make sense he was way over there?
How did he cover all that distance he
is looking at me he pays no mind to the
Imperial gods, just me.
He must know I am the Emperor, in
which case I must be his target.
He is going to kill me.
But wait, I have my Kaiser armor and
Kaiser sword, both made of or a calcum.
What was that?
Have a change of heart?
Why the hell are our cannons
sticking out of the ground like that?
What in God's name is going on?
I had 10,000 soldiers that
were all perfectly equipped.
And aeguses that could defend
against dragon's breath.
Even the Brionac can
burn dragons to a crisp.
How are they now all
broken down and worthless?
Please, you must tell me who you are.
And why haven't you killed me yet?
No, not that weapon.
King Clay's Black Blade.
The one dungeon relic I
covet above all others.
Why does this man have it?
No, don't be.
Wait, that sword is made
from an unknown metal.
It is supposed to be too heavy
for any normal human to carry.
I have heard even that freakishly strong
king needed both hands to wield it.
There's no way anyone
could surpass King Klai's.
But that's the only way to
explain what I'm seeing.
This man has done it.
My god, he did all of this.
I himself.
The only reason I am still
alive is because he wants me to
endure the torture of humiliation
before finishing me off.
I just know it.
He is going to do to me exactly what
I was planning to do to King Clays.
Huh?
It hurts.
Oh?
Oh!
Thank
you
so
much for watching.